You're leaving already, Lord Odin?
He may cause trouble,
but I'll still miss him.
I heard word there's a
monster living in Kuri.
An ogre called Ashura Doji.
Hmm.
Kuri's a blight on this land.
Even the Shogun cannot control it.
If the criminal takes refuge in Kuri,
the authorities are
powerless to apprehend him.
But if they lack the strength to survive
there, they'll be chewed up and spit out.
It's a lawless land, almost
like a different country.
Interesting, perhaps I should
take a tour around Wano.
Have a safe trip, Odin!
Keen, Denjiro, come visit us again.
See ya.
He shows up uninvited and leaves just
as suddenly He values his freedom.
Lord Yasui
Come look, hurry
This is the room that Lord Odin stayed in.
Why on earth would he do such a thing?
We must send him a bill
for repairs at once.
Let's just pretend there
was a natural disaster.
If you're too soft on him,
he'll take advantage of you.
Lord Yasui!
What is it now?
The money is missing?
Yes, I'm certain I put it in
the safe, my lord. Um. Hmm?
It pains me dearly to say this.
But I'm afraid that the money was stolen.
I saw it.
It was Lord Odin.
He slipped it into his robe
and walked away without a word.
I knew it was that scoundrel.
Biting the hand that feeds
him is what he's doing.
He'll pay.
Would Odin bother being sneaky?
Are you sure, Orochi?
Yes, forgive me
I was too afraid.
I should have made an effort to stop him.
After leaving Hakumai, Oden and his
followers continued onward to Kuri,
causing trouble all along the way.
How much longer are
you going to follow me?
Why forever?
Because we're your
biggest fans, Lord Odin.
He's annoyed.
Hey, why are you standing
in the rain, you idiots?
As your retainers, we must protect
you Come on, you're going to get sick.
On our way!
What are you doing in here?
I am writing a journal.
They say it is a navigator's duty.
A daily observance on ships overseas.
The following are excerpts from Odin's
journal, chronicling his adventures.
In Ringo, we met some ragged little
ruts, a pair of starving siblings.
Get out of here!
They tried to earn money by dancing,
but people were as cold as the snow.
Why do you little agents
keep following me?
That food isn't yours.
Are you listening?
Put that back.
They were the children of
a great master of dance.
But their families split apart
when their father was arrested.
They brazenly ate our Odin without
my permission, sobbing all the while.
Impossible to deter.
In Koby, there was a goblin of a man who
cut the hair off the living and dead alike,
carrying it away into the night.
As it turns out, he sold brushes
made from human hair for a living.
Whoa! I give up! I give up!
I thought you were dead!
After I gave him a good wallop,
he strangely decided to follow me.
He claimed to be a long-suffering victim
of persecution, but he likely deserved it.
In the deep forests of Uda,
tales of a notorious mountain
bandit were carried on the wind.
They say he would abduct women
and beat men half to death.
Why are you following me, too?
Funny, right?
Hmm.
Is that the mountain bandit?
You're okay!
In truth, the bandit was
a skilled ninja, Raizo,
who quit the Kozuki clan's Oniwabanshu
after Okunoichi broke his heart.
I can't live my life in hiding anymore!
Please take me with you!
He's annoyed!
Kozuki Oden came here?
He's the son of the shogun.
Killing him should be fun.
Go and bring him to me. Yes, sir!
More than anything, I love to see
the high and mighty brought low.
Hey, where did Odin go?
He went to take a dump,
I think. Been a while.
That was yesterday.
You know how he is.
He'll disappear for a day or two
on a whim with no explanation.
Uh, he went south.
Isn't there a gate to
Cootie south of here?
You're right!
Damn it all!
I told him I would die for him!
And then I let him sneak
off to battle alone!
The place I entered was
like a different world.
The stench of death filled the air,
and a violent wave thick like
blood seemed to aim itself at me.
Time to say goodbye to
your head, Kozuki Oden.
Let's go!
I'm not alone!
There are people who live in this dream.
I'm not sure if we were ever to come.
I'm not scared of me.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
So you're the famous Kozuki Orenk!
I've been disavowed!
I no longer have a name.
Anyone can enter, but those who try
to leave will be promptly killed.
Especially samurai like you.
Sounds suffocating.
Huh?
You've made a cage.
Watch in yourself when you can be free.
I didn't ask for your input. What?
You were foolish enough to come here,
so here you'll remain until your death.
Which I expect will be imminent.
So no one can leave.
Now it's personal!
That's my least favorite rule!
It's my turf, so they're my rules.
Now die!
Whoa!
You run this hellhole! Hahaha! Ha,
ha!
Odin!
We're coming!
Just stay where you are!
Look, he must have
broken through that gate!
This hellhole is the only
home that I will ever know.
A pampered bastard like you
could never understand my life.
Are you telling me this
is the life that you want?
Look!
He's up there!
Stop him!
Odin!
We'll help you fight!
You're a moment too late.
I just wrapped up here. My apologies.
I fought all day and all
night, but it is done.
Why don't you kill me already?
I know there's no future for me.
I'll die with no regrets.
Is this Ashura Doji?
Their leader?
Listen to me, all of you.
Are you still willing to
follow me to the bitter end?
I need your aid, your strength, your wit.
For I have decided to lift up
the people of this cursed land
by becoming their king!
I come bearing news of young
Lord Odin What happened?
What did he do this time?
Take a look
Kuri has been tamed
Only Odin could accomplish this I
see it, but I can scarcely believe it
The people of Kuri will ruff around the
edges but filled with boundless energy.
Thanks to Odin's loyal companions
and headstrong leadership,
they turned their blood-soaked
land into a place worth living,
and the rest of Wano
could not help but notice.
In response to this accomplishment,
the shogun Kozuki Sukiyaki
retracted his disvowel.
and instead gave his son
the title Daimyo of Kuri.
Look!
Lord Odin is going to be
a dying yo for real now!
Yeah!
Then Cootie will be a
full-fledged province!
We pulled it off!
All that hard work was worth it!
King's all right.
We knew you could do it
from the start, Lord Odin!
I'm so proud of you!
Congratulations, Odin!
Now Cootie will finally be your winner!
All right, friends!
I'm the Gaimyo!
Yeah!
You're looking dour, Asheran.
This is new to me.
I...
I have never known peace before.
Thank you, Odin.
I owe you my...
Stop it!
You're creeping me!
I was being sincere!
Huh?
What are you doing? No!
Stop!
You should be celebrating!
You know, a proper Daimyo needs retainers.
I'm sure there are many
wise and prudent candidates.
But you're the only ones I want.
What say you?
Will you be my samurai?
No, it's not coming out of your noses!
No, it's on me!
Disgusting! Stop!
Six years passed in Wano without incident.
But across the seas, there
was a great storm brewing.
33 years before the present day,
the remnants of the legendary rocks
pirates began to form into their own crews,
with their strongest
members becoming infamous.
and influential in their own right.
What are they? Animals?
Just hairy men?
What odd creatures they are.
Did you get it?
Think so?
Long ago,
several hundred years ago in fact,
the Minx and the Kozuki samurai
from the land of Wano made a pledge.
We swore to be steadfast
allies through thick and thin.
Stupid waddo!
I hate it here!
Dear country, stop!
Get me down, dammit!
Help!
I'm just a Cape!
You're all monsters!
We shouldn't have set
sail in the first place!
Coming here was a tough idea!
Some sworn allies you gotta are!
A cat monster, a dog
monster, and a Cape too.
I'm starting to feel like
this whole beach is cursed.
Let's burn them!
This should be enough fish for the vinyl!
We're gonna die!
Help us!
Let them go!
Such cruelty!
Shame on you!
The only reason you fear them is
because they're different than you.
But those are children you bastards
tried to burn at the stake!
Thank you, Kara!
Farewell!
You're just gonna leave us here!
Uh, why are there weird
little animals here?
They followed me.
Thank you, Grove, for rescuing us!
Hot!
Yeah, we almost starved,
we almost drowned,
and then we almost got
burned to death, too!
Ah! Ah!
Damn it!
This is way too hot to eat!
Yeah, no, this is unnatural.
They should not be talking like that.
Ah, delightful.
Father told me about minks like you.
Then I was right!
I knew as soon as I saw that
symbol, we had it back home, too.
where they say our
nations are like brothers.
Yugaru saved our lives.
We were so hungry. Of course.
Eat as much as you like.
Don't mind if I do.
Like radish?
You should try a bite.
It does look good, actually.
Now try the fish cake.
How is it?
It's too hot!
Yes, it's not sensitive to us, okay?
You've ruined it, you damn fool!
Oh, hey, stop it!
I'm sorry, Cat, but heat
is the spice of life!
And wooded was born to boil!
That's so cool!
It tastes good to me.
Who are you supposed to be?
A castaway, in simple terms.
My mother and I were shipwrecked.
We asked for help, but people threw
rocks at us because we're fishmen.
Unfortunately, my mother was struck
down, so we couldn't return home.
Before she died, she said to me,
The people above hate fishmen.
If you want to survive, then you
must tell them you're a kappa.
I'm Kawamatsu the kappa.
I've been living off leftovers.
Thank you for saving my life.
And thank you for treating me.
To such a delicious meal.
I will never forget this.
May I eat the rest of the Odin now please?
Not yet.
We'll make some more, just wait.
That's not necessary.
It's still edible.
Oh no.
I've been a bad guest haven't I?
I wasted all that good food.
You're being very mature.
I am so sorry!
I'll beat it!
That's no way too hot!
What a funny little creature!
Stop it!
How splendid.
The world is full of people
and creatures to see.
Meeting all of you has renewed my
determination to set sail and discover more!
That's right!
This world's full of great stuff!
Well, take care then.
Huh?
Hey!
Didn't you go to hear us?
We have nowhere else to go!
All right, all right!
Just get off of me!
It happened again. Sure did!
As you're terrible at saying no!
Speaking of which, we really
need to talk about our finances.
You've got to stop lending money
to Orochi without asking me.
The guy's a total scumbag.
Well, even if he's independent now,
he's still one of Yasui's associates.
But he needs help.
Sneaking, slinking, silence.
Got it?
Those are the basics. Yes, sir.
Onward, think nothing of Yasui.
Sneaking, slinking, silence.
What were you thinking trying
to steal all this money?
Our Lord Odin's running
short on cash, okay?
If you're gonna kill us, then
just do it, damn hedgehog.
But you should know that we'd
do anything to help our Lord.
I'll give my life if that's what it takes.
What a mess.
Where do you find these people, Odin?
I'll let you keep the stolen money.
Please reconsider.
Hakumai needs those
funds more than they do.
Also...
Here.
While we're at it, take
this, too. It's yours.
Wait, more money?
There has to be some kind of catch.
Is this a trap?
Do you truly love Odin?
If that's the case, then use this
money to clean yourselves up.
Buy some books, learn some
manners, get educated.
Look at us!
Yes, sir!
No, from the gut! Yes, sir!
Having a bunch of unruly thugs as
retainers will only bring shame to Odin.
Lord Odin, I thank thee once more for
a bountiful feast on this fine day.
Such piquancy, it's quite exquisite.
What's gotten into you?
Why are you talking that way?
One day I'm sure he will become the
shogun of the land of Wano. Therefore,
those who support him
must not only be loyal,
They must be the finest
seminar in the country.
It goes without saying that
you must protect your lord.
But the people of Wano will
come to depend on you as well.
You must be a symbol of our
strength, our guardian deity.
The Daimyo of Kuri is making
a visit to the capital today.
I heard Lord Odin's retainers
are a bunch of thugs.
Don't get robbed.
Look, they're coming down
the street right now.
Those are proper-looking samurais!
Were Lord Odin's retainers
always so gallant?
No, not like this.
It's like a shogun's procession.
The heroic side of these samurai
was such a wonder to behold
that the entire capital seemed to
let on a collective gasp. Indeed,
it was said that the
weight of their arrival was
so great that the city
itself sunk ever so slightly.
It's been a while, father.
My son, what a welcome surprise.
I hear you've become a great leader.
My retainers have made me great.
I'm no different than when I left here.
You're showing gratitude to others?
You don't need to be scared.
Oden rushed to the capital when he
heard that his father had fallen ill.
But seeing his son again seemed
to invigorate the Shogun.
However, this is the last time
that the two would exchange words.
Seems people live on this island.
Pops, it's going to take at
least a week to patch this up.
The water ruined all our cargo.
First off, we need to
get food and supplies.
Who wants to go?
Most of us, probably.
We all gotta stretch our legs, don't we?
We just climbed up a waterfall.
Yet there's sea here
and an island somehow.
Trouble, sir.
We need your help quick.
What is it?
Calm yourself.
You're too loud.
There's a giant pirate ship
ducked at Itachi board.
A pirate ship?
Lord Odin, where are you going?
To the port!
Go, go, go!
All right, then.
We'll go get food and supplies.
And I'll come with you. No way.
I told you no deckhands allowed.
Ah, don't be like that.
Hey, Pops, I can go with the crew, right?
Do what you want.
You heard us. Off we go!
Yeah, and you heard me say no. Now stay.
Wait, what?
Port Odin ran off to the port.
Why did you let him go?
I heard a pirate ship
showed up out of nowhere.
You say it looks real crazy!
It's bigger than our ships,
and the pirates look tough.
Stop him at any cost!
Surely he's just going there
to take the pirates away?
Not a chance!
You know that this is his dream, right?
He wants to set sail.
That must be it.
The pirate ship.
Finally.
Freedom—we're in trouble!
All
of you need to stand back;
someone's coming for us,
someone extraordinary—glad
you could make it!
Breathing the storms, climbing the
waterfall—we don't get many visitors here.
many visitors here
Hello, pirates!
I've been waiting for you!
I like you, old man!
You're gonna pay!
I'll teach you a thing or two, boy! Hey!
I've been waiting for
someone like you, Pirate!
My name is Press Gjolden!
I don't know who you are,
but you're my ticket out!
Take me with you! Huh?